on this Sunday night on the voice government shutdown now just over 24 hours away tonight who is to blame and the wheel for millions
在这个星期天晚上在语音政府关闭现在只要超过24小时的路程，今晚是谁的错与车轮数以百万计
who is following u turns out on social networking your friends the government surveillance like it or not
谁是下ü原来在社交你的朋友，政府的监视喜欢还是不喜欢
troubled waters the toxic Lana coastline what can be done about the pollution of a paradise
浑水摸鱼的有毒拉娜海岸线什么可以做关于天堂的污染
how many jump from 6000 feet and wellness between a rock and a hard place
有多少6000英尺，健康岩石和硬的地方之间跳
NBC News world headquarters in New York
NBC新闻全球总部设在纽约
this is NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt
这是NBC晚间新闻与莱斯特·霍尔特
things are looking good when a little under 30 hours away from a partial shutdown of the federal government appointed which Washington will be unable to pay my bills leaving a lot of people without a paycheck
事情看起来很好，当在30小时的路程，从任命为联邦政府的华盛顿将无法支付我的账单留下了很多的人没有薪水的部分关闭了一点
mechanics of avoiding a Monday night shutdown a pretty straightforward assemble vote by Congress to keep the money flowing with do it
避免了周一晚上关机一个非常简单的组装由国会表决，以保持资金与流动力学做
what is coarse is usually the politics not the mechanics interpreting to be the obstacles and a partisan b**** during the week come to know as business as usual
什么是粗通常是政治不解释是在一周的障碍和党派b ****的机制来知道作为照常营业
weather was on 4 display last night a rare Saturday night session of the House of Representatives not a good sign with full coverage starting on Capitol Hill with Kelly O'Donnell dating Kelly where we stand
天气在4显示昨晚众议院的一个罕见的周六晚上会不会与全覆盖开始在国会山与凯利·奥唐奈约会凯莉我们所处的位置好兆头
well after what makes this feel different than other showdown prices in recent years old parties are sugar coating it actually predict there will be a shut down and there's none of that frantic vaccine negotiation going on
以及之后是什么使这感觉比其他摊牌的价格不同，近年来老方是糖衣它实际上预测会有一个关机和有没有那个疯狂的疫苗谈判正在进行
and while it is still possible to see it seems more and more on likely that they can avoid this mess
虽然它仍然可以看到它似乎越来越多的可能，他们可以避开这个烂摊子
the bill is passed without objection to motion to reconsider is light on a table
该法案获得通过无异议的运动重新考虑轻放在桌子
high stakes what lower expectations for Capitol Hill
对于国会山高赌注什么期望低
late today House Republicans notably Speaker John Boehner together to pull out senators for not coming to work today and we want to work and go she ate I get the job done conservative hailedabear risky demand
今天晚了众议院共和党人尤其是议长博纳一起拔出参议员不来上班今天，我们要努力去她吃我把工作做好保守hailedabear风险的需求
refusing to find the government is the president healthcare law is layed one year Democrats will wait until tomorrow to reject the house plan
拒绝找政府是总统的医疗保健法律奠定1年民主党将等到明天否决众议院计划
this is the old football strategy
这是旧的足球策略
when you get to where you want to be in a football game you're on out the clock
当你到哪里你想在一场足球比赛你在出来的时钟
Democratic leaders say the Tea Party delay is going nowhere
民主党领导人说，茶党延迟是无处可去
there's a time and place to debate Obama care
有一个时间和地点进行辩论奥巴马护理
the house this morning
房子今天上午
should not shut the government down
不应该关上​​了政府下来
what is on earth are we doing here Republicans did pastor plan to keep the government open with conditions when your delay of the president's healthcare law repeal of a manufacturer's tax on medical devices
什么是地球上的我们在这里做的共和党人做了牧师的计划，以保持政府与开放条件时，你的总统的医疗保健法律的一个制造商的税，医疗器械废除延迟
and if there is a shutdown the military with still get paid on time tea party forced Texas senator Ted Cruz strategy on Meet the Press
如果有一个关机军事与仍然按时支付茶话会被迫德州参议员特德·克鲁兹战略遇见新闻
the American people overwhelmingly reject Obamacare the understand its not working the only people who are listening to the argument are the career politicians in Washington
美国人民压倒多数拒绝的Obamacare的理解它不工作谁在听的说法的唯一的人是职业政客在华盛顿
but tonight old client corridors of power seat empty
电动座椅，但今晚老客户的走廊空
1 day left before the government lights go out
剩下1天前政府灯熄灭
Kelly O'Donnell NBC News the capital
凯利·奥唐奈NBC新闻的资本
Michelle Franzen New York tour boats mod with visitors headed to the Statue of Liberty on Ellis Island today become Tuesday Lady Liberty National Parks coast to coast for clothes
国防部与游客米歇尔·弗兰岑纽约游览船今天前往自由女神在埃利斯岛雕像成为周二自由女神国家公园东海岸到西海岸的衣服
the first visible impact if the government shuts down to the Statue of Liberty hostage is a poly me in the nation's capital tours of the Washington Monument the Smithsonian National Zoo what also closed
如果政府关闭以自由人质的雕像的第一个可见的影响是聚我在华盛顿纪念碑史密森国家动物园国家的首都之旅什么也收
along with your cemetery Mount Rushmore and the Battle of Lake Mead outlet
随着你的墓地拉什莫尔山和米德湖出口战役
leisure definition of bread and butter to surrounding businesses like Boulder boats
像博尔德船周边企业休闲的面包和奶油的定义
what happened to a business shutter sound come out your sometimes 56 times a day doing White Castle um about the lake is everything we have
发生了什么事业务快门声音出来你有时56天做白色城堡嗯对湖景的时间就是一切，我们有
the last time the government shutdown was in the mid 90's for 3 weeks National Park Service employee my clitoris list for less then and worries it will happen again
最后一次政府关闭是在90年代中期3周国家公园管理处员工我的阴蒂名单小于和忧虑它会再次发生
we have employees that have to have family to take care of a bills to pay how we are very concerned about the about the effect on them for any sort of shutdown
我们有必须有家庭采取的照顾票据支付，我们怎么都非常关注有关的任何形式的停机对他们的影响的员工
the impact a national park visitors it's just the start of an economic ripple effect 800
影响一个国家公园游人它是一个经济连锁反应800仅仅是开始
did the shutdown drags on October 17th the steaks grow even higher
10月17日没有关机拖动牛排增长甚至更高
Congress doesn't raise the debt ceiling and the US Treasury can't meet us obligations that could raise interest rates mortgage rates credit card rates and plans the economy back in recession cost in everyman
国会不提高债务上限和美国财政部不能满足我们可能加息抵押贷款利率信用卡利率债务，并计划将经济重新陷入衰退的成本在普通人
with all the possible for low the National Park closing Paris il some some programs that will remain on such that the government shuts down including mail service delivery funding for security Social Security and also air traffic controllers and screeners at airport
与所有可能低的国家公园关闭巴黎IL一些一些程序将保持这样的政府关闭，包括邮件服务经费保障社会安全，也是空中交通管制员和安检员在机场
Michelle Franzen and Kelly O'Donnell legs where we stand what to take for morning how this is likely to play out words gone by NBC Sports director and chief White House correspondent Chuck Todd Chuck
米歇尔·弗兰岑和Kelly O'Donnell的腿我们的立场采取什么早上这是怎么可能发挥出了由NBC体育总监兼首席白宫记者查托德查词
well after I could tell you what's going on here at the White House not much of anything President Obama convene the meeting of his senior staff
好后，我可以告诉你发生了什么事情在此间举行的白宫没有太多东西总统奥巴马召集他的高级工作人员会议
earlier today where they talk about Natalie what's going on with the government shutdown tall so don't forget to is day is the day of open enrollment 4
今天早些时候，他们谈论娜塔莉什么与政府关闭高大的事情，所以不要忘了是一天开放注册4天
Residence Inn Detroit health care law so all of that coming together coincidentally on that front what's tomorrow's gonna look like with the Senate will do with deal sometime tomorrow afternoon
Residence Inn酒店底特律医疗保健法，使所有这一切在这一方面走到一起不约而同什么是明天的会看起来像参议院将与交易做一段时间明天下午
send a bill back to the house
发送账单回屋
NFL point sometime between I say dinner time tomorrow night and midnight the House of Representatives is likely to send back one more Bill Lester
NFL点之间的某个时候我说吃饭时间明天晚上和午夜众议院很可能会回送多一个比尔莱斯特
maybe it's a clean bill whithers no writers or anything like that that would keep the government open for sale week or maybe it only has one demand on it that medical device tax that use all but this isn't over yet it's likely to see one more active display before the government does
也许这是一个干净的法案whithers没有作家或类似的，将保持政府公开售星期或也许它只有在它的一个需求是使用所有的医疗设备税，但这还没有结束，它很可能看到一个更为什么政府不主动显示之前
will be watching this play alright thanks my Chuck Todd when is this weekend about a major component of a government secrets surveillance program 18 may not be cut
将密切关注这部戏好吗感谢我查托德时，这个周末约一个政府秘密监视计划18的主要组成部分可能不会被削减
back to haunt those of us who live in brass the Republic nature of social networking we got the shores of NBC's national investigative correspondent Michael Isikoff
回过头来困扰我们这些谁住在黄铜的社交网络，我们得到了NBC的全国调查记者迈克尔Isikoff沿岸共和国性质
more classified documents leaked by ex contractor in federal fugitive Edward Snowden disclosure another program that secretly collects personal data on American citizens the documents revealed today by the New York Times
由前承包商在联邦逃犯爱德华·斯诺登披露泄露更多机密文件的其他程序暗中收集美国公民的个人数据文件今天透露，纽约时报
show the agency cens 2011 this been building large scale graphics of fun intelligence networks
表明该机​​构经社2011这已经建设有趣的情报网络的大规模图形
include social connections of some American citizens
包括一些美国公民的社会关系
accessing their Facebook and Twitter accounts bank codes airline passenger manifest and even GPS location
访问他们的Facebook和Twitter账户的银行代码航空公司的旅客名单，甚至GPS定位
government is putting together databases personalize a professional eyes um basically tell a comprehensive story of how we are living everyday
政府正在组建的数据库个性化的专业的眼睛嗯，基本上告诉我们如何生活的日常全面讲述
Beyonce said the statement that all queries in Stata must be conducted for a fun intelligence purpose of a rare public hearing of the Senate
碧昂斯表示，在Stata的所有查询必须为参议院的罕见的公开听证会的一个有趣的智力目的所进行的陈述
committee US intelligence officials last week vigorously defended the NSA surveillance efforts and once again denounce the week spice node
委员会美国情报官员上周大力捍卫了国家安全局的监测工作，并再次谴责一周香料节点
there's no way to racer make up for the Damaja we know is already been done
有没有办法来赛车，弥补Damaja我们知道的是已经完成
continue to dodge questions about what they are collecting about Americans during this exchanger cell site that I can track where a person is Ben from the cell phone in your pocket
继续对他们这种交换单元在现场收集有关美国人躲闪什么问题，我可以跟踪，当一个人是奔的手机在你的口袋里
how does the NSA ever collected
如何在国家安全局收集过
or ever made any plans to collect American cell site information
或者做过任何计划，收集美国小区站点信息
what I don't want to do senator is pulled out in a non classified forum anything is classified here
我不想做参议员被拉出在非机密的论坛什么是归类在这里
will food uses of water for supported by NBC News inspector general disclose in 12 ounces is 2003 employee spying on their girlfriends boyfriends and spouses Webster
将水食品用途由NBC新闻总监支持12盎司披露的2003员工刺探他们的女朋友的男朋友和配偶韦伯斯特
Michael Isikoff tonight in Arizona investigators release to 120 page report leaves almost as many questions answers about why 19 firefighters died in the urinal Hill Fire it was the worst firefighting tragedy since 9 11
迈克尔Isikoff今晚在亚利桑那州调查人员发放120页的报告树叶几乎同样多的问题的答案，为什么19消防员在小便池山火死亡，这是最坏的消防悲剧，因为9 11
and we'll be official report is complete some victims family members want more
我们会在正式报告完成一些受害者家属希望有更多
NBC's Miguel Almaguer cover the story and has a report tonight
NBC的米格尔Almaguer报道这一事件，并有今晚的报告
radio transmissions are believed to be some of the final communications from the Granite Mountain hotshots shortly after this video was taken
无线电传输被认为是一些来自花岗岩山能人最终通信的这段视频被拍摄后不久，
1908 firefighters lost their lives in Arizona investigators now believe based on a 3 month investigation poorly programmed radios made communication major problem
1908消防队员丧生在亚利桑那州调查人员现在认为，基于3个月的调查程序不好使无线电通信专业问题
just before flame swept over the hotshot there was a 33 minutes radio black
就在火焰席卷了炙手可热的有一个33分钟无线电黑色
nothing will bring them home
什么都不会带他们回家
Juliet Ashcraft and her 4 children lost Andrew
朱丽叶阿什克拉夫特和她的4个孩子失去了安德鲁
that being my husband and 11 for large families I'm ok with 30 minutes and accounted for
那是我的丈夫和11的大家庭，我确定有30分钟，占
the report says the Hot Shots were in a safe sound when for unknown reasons be descended into a valley when Cruise could not run fire spreading at 12
该报告说，热的射击是在一个安全的声音时，不知什么原因被陷入低谷时，克鲁斯不能运行在火蔓延12
our state employee emergency shelters what temperatures exceeded 2000 grease no one knows why the main headed into the valley
我们的国家职工应急避难场所什么温度超过2000油脂没有人知道为什么主要领导进了山谷
when the Hot Shots were surrounded by flames a DC 10 full of fire retardant with overhang
当热的射击是由火焰直流10全阻燃带悬包围
the air tanker never received a cruise location Michelle Parker says her son Wade died with his brothers
空中加油机从未收到巡航位置米歇尔·帕克说，她的儿子韦德与他的兄弟死了
faded everything they could
褪色的一切，他们可以
the report places no plane
该报告没有放置平面
19 families never got to say goodbye and now they may never have answers Miguel Almaguer NBC News Los Angeles
19家庭从来没有说再见，现在他们可能永远不会有答案米格尔Almaguer NBC新闻洛杉矶
overseas a week after terrorist gun down and tortured essence of people inside a popular mall in Nairobi Kenya NBCNews obtain fotos a show what does cm look like after the attack
海外后一个星期恐怖分子枪里面的人一个受欢迎的商场在内罗毕肯尼亚NBCNews下来，折磨精髓得到FOTOS表演什么呢厘米的样子后攻
investigators say they taking a nice ass back into custody the latest on all this from NBC's Ron Allen in Nairobi
调查人员说，他们采取一个不错的屁股后面羁押最新的这一切都来自NBC的罗恩·艾伦在内罗毕
these exclusive pictures reveal the order devastation inside the Rubyz Westgate Mall four floors of upscale stores and restaurants like many malls in suburban America it was crowded with families enjoying a typical Saturday afternoon
这些独家照片揭示了秩序破坏的Rubyz梅龙镇广场四层高档商店和餐馆像许多商场在美国郊区的人们挤满了家人享受一个典型的周六下午内
now good staying with blood after 4 days of warfare
经过4天的战争与血现在住好
between 10 to 15 Milton Union forces thats whats up the food court surprisingly Samaria scene untouched the grocery
10〜15米尔顿联盟部队之间那怎么了美食广场出奇的撒玛利亚场景不变的杂货店
where is where sources say the most intense fighting took place today can u leaders Stonewall the government report the temperature in recent warnings about a possible attack
哪里是哪里的消息来源说战斗最激烈的今天发生了u能领导石墙政府报告有关可能的攻击在最近警告的温度
the Westgate Mall
梅龙镇广场
also today a mystery song
今天也是一个谜歌
who is the mother scene in the video protecting her children all of them playing dead until help arrived
谁是母亲场景中的视频保护她的孩子们个个玩死了，直到救援人员到达
end of times a day should a bullet casing on your mother gunpowder
一天的时间到底应该对你母亲的火药子弹外壳
Luling is Mel safely home with her son ties Dr Seiss Houston born a half hours on the floor keeping her young energetic children wife
庐陵是梅尔安全回家与她的儿子绑乌尔休斯顿博士出生在地板上一个半小时让她精力充沛的年轻夫妇的孩子
listen to Wiz Khalifa not bring peace protectors provide a way out for us
听奇才哈利法不能带来和平保护提供了一种方式为我们
hope to find out who the officer is and thank you for saving the family
希望能找出谁是官是，感谢你救了全家
acrostic Ogden down to Nigeria were gunman storm a college campus in the middle of the night killing as many as 50 students as they slept most of the day
藏头诗奥格登下降到尼日利亚是枪手风波大学校园中的夜杀多达50名学生，因为他们睡了大半天的中间
believed to be there late teens in 20s Nigerian official suspect the attackers were Islamic militants got no conclusive evidence yet
相信是有十几岁的20岁尼日利亚官方嫌疑袭击者被伊斯兰武装分子有没有确凿的证据尚
return to Iran and increasing size of a changing relationship between a country and the United States after so many years of hostility
返回伊朗和经过这么多年的敌对国家与美国之间不断变化的关系，规模日益扩大
when President Obama called in Iran president rouhani on Friday many views did as a sign of progress what do Iranian swallow c** warming with the West NBC's alia Lucy got out of the streets of Tehran NSM
当奥巴马总统在伊朗总统rouhani呼吁周五很多观点确实是一种进步的表现有什么伊朗燕子C **与西方NBC的特别露西离开了德黑兰NSM的街道升温
supporters of the possibility of a recess in relations with the west
的凹槽的可能性，与西方的关系支持者
what is the Traxxas 2075 talking to President Obama running shoes in pokemon is called with tomatoes and eggs
什么是的Traxxas 2075谈论奥巴马总统在口袋妖怪跑鞋被调用，西红柿和鸡蛋
hardline newspapers Road death to America honeys return criticizing for giving too much I'm getting nothing back
强硬派报纸路死亡美国蜂蜜返回批评给太多我得到任何回报
honey to solve a dispute on people expect him to pick
蜂蜜来解决人们的纠纷指望他来接
I've been walking around the streets of town on dating the movie monster people about how they feel about better relationship with the United States everybody without question favorite better relationship they want to run to come in from the cold
我已经走在小镇的街道上约会电影怪物的人他们是如何感受毫无疑问的喜爱与美国大家更好的关系，关系比较好，他们要运行从寒冷来
change
变化
Pizza Inn
比萨酒店
lucky people want to go to America able to do a ship
幸运的人想要去美国能够做一个船
my camera catches a single mothers
我的相机捕捉一个单身母亲
Porter self 16 year old daughter
波特自16岁女儿
she told me the lost years everything is becoming so expensive she worries about her daughters afros future
她告诉我失去的岁月一切都变得如此昂贵，她担心她的女儿afros未来
she wants to study your medicine specialty in America what she said St Petersburg Obama we should I peel the countries
她想研究你的医学专业在美国她说什么圣彼得堡奥巴马我们我要剥国家
the real test willkommen world powers
真正的考验willkommen世界大国
Geneva middle how to deal with the issue easy NBC News Tara
日内瓦中间如何处理这个问题容易NBC新闻塔拉
when Nightly News continues on this Sunday what's behind
当晚间新闻继续在这个星期天有什么背后
major environmental crisis part of the coastline
海岸线的重大环境危机的一部分
away in a prayer the man who gets his throat twice in a row opening between
走在祈祷谁得到他的喉咙两次之间的一排开的男人
in Florida situs a time is running out for a vital water weigh now so polluted soon the damage could be irreversible thousands protest
在佛罗里达州的拓扑时间已经不多了至关重要的水掂量现在这么快污染的损害可能是不可逆的数千名抗议
salami Indian River Lagoon this weekend fighting to get attention for the dying estuary East Coast threat we get more tonight from NBC's mark Potter
萨拉米印第安河泻湖这个周末争取得到重视的垂死河口东海岸的威胁，我们从NBC的标志波特得到更多的今晚
what is the drug millions of dollars a year now found people to stay out of the water to avoid infection rashes and nausea
什么是药物数百万美元一年，现在发现人留出来的水，以避免感染皮疹和恶心
not only be on critical hits does asterisk rages people are outrage
不仅是对暴击确实星号肆虐人们的愤怒
Mary read a bar manager repair marina in Stuart Florida
玛丽看了酒吧经理修码头在佛罗里达州斯图尔特
body is very concerned about touching the water
身体是非常关心接触水
these pictures of noxious algae by her dog
有害藻类通过她的狗这些图片
it burns your eyes your throat that has a lot of different uncomfortable a fax
它燃烧你的眼睛你的喉咙，有很多不同的难受传真的
the trouble with Harry is 156 miles long Indian River Lagoon system home to 4300 plant and animal species is one of America's most violent
与哈里的麻烦为156英里长印第安河泻湖体系回家4300植物和动物物种是美国最暴力的1
say and sewage from agriculture
从农业说，排污
LG killing wildlife is where messin with Mother Nature
LG的杀戮野生动物在这里与大自然的messin
and we don't want to get to the point of no return
我们不想去的不归路
normally this sandbar especially on weekend is coming along the edges buy boots in sunbathers but now with all that algae and posted health warnings most people are staying away
通常这个沙洲特别是在周末来临沿边缘买靴子的日光浴，但现在所有的藻类和发布健康警告大多数人都避而远之
is upset release date
生气的发布日期
in the North
在北
usually high number of manatees dolphins and pelicans have died this year federal and state plans to protect water flows in removing nutrients are not yet fully funded
平时大量的海牛和海豚鹈鹕今年已去世联邦和各州的计划，以保护去除营养物的水流还没有充分的资金
I'm angry needs to be fixed its not AAA it's not rocket science fair solutions they're all political solutions
我很生气的需求是固定的它不是AAA级这不是火箭科学公平的解决方案，他们都是政治解决方案
sinus Warner Supertech the lagoon must be consuming too late to save water weigh
窦华纳仕霸泻湖必须耗费来不及节约用水权衡
mark Potter NBC News Stuart Florida
马克·波特NBC新闻佛罗里达州斯图尔特
add up next week Antony this Sunday night wear big time college football coach was sacked this weekend
加起来下周安东尼这个星期天的晚上穿大时间大学橄榄球教练被解职本周末
138.wav
10 minutes on the water today in London one of those tourist duck boats caught fire on the River Thames
今天10分钟的水在伦敦的旅游鸭子船之一起火泰晤士河
30 people were on board many jump in the water to avoid the flames were quickly rescued by police firefighters and passing boat all the passengers were counted for 8 a.m. Were treated for smoke inhalation and other minor injuries
30人在船上许多跳在水中，以免火苗很快就被警察消防员救出，并通过船上所有乘客被计算在上午08点共治疗吸入浓烟和其他轻伤
back in this country of course correction report tonight in big time college football just hours after a crushing lost to Arizona State USC announce the firing of coach Lane Kiffin USC athletic directors at it was just time to make a change
回来的路线修正，今晚在大时代的大学橄榄球几个小时后报告这个国家的破碎输给亚利桑那州南加州大学宣布主帅巷Kiffin USC体育主管它的发射只是时间做出改变
Trojans of now watch 7 over last 11 games by the way to score in last night's game Arizona State 62 USC 41
现在木马观看7比去年11场比赛的得分方式在昨晚的比赛亚利桑那州62南加州大学41
and he was a scene in Olympia Greece this morning with a torch for the SOC games list using the sun's rays in America flameless passed on to a Greek spear
今天上午，他在希腊奥林匹亚的场景与火炬使用的太阳光线在传递给希腊长矛美国无焰SOC的游戏名单
goodwill open in the travel across Russia is 9 time zones leaving make a stop in space as cosmonauts taken unlit torch for space walk
商誉在俄罗斯各地的旅游开放是9个时区使留在太空中的停止而采取熄灭火炬太空行走宇航员
and in a moment when a man known for gliding for waterfalls and diving of mountains in Mich he is scared by son you know you gotta see it and you will
在一个时刻，当一个人出名的滑翔的瀑布和高山密歇根州，他由儿子害怕，你知道你要看到它的潜水，你会
find me tonight it's kind of snake you know you should be watching with your eyes closed but you can't help yourself it was all about Jim Corliss in a wingsuit diving 6000 feet into the history books this weekend in China NBC's in Williams was there
找我今晚它的一种蛇，你知道你应该闭上你的眼睛可以看，但你不能帮助自己它是所有关于吉姆·科利斯在翼装高空跳伞潜水6000英尺入历史本周末在中国NBC的威廉斯在那里
is target a man to fly through the narrow credits on the right between the Soaring rocks of China's John Lennon Mountain
目标是一个人通过对中国的约翰·列侬山的岩石飙升之间的权利狭窄的学分飞
Manship coolest upset stomach the Flying Daggers is most challenging yes the Saturday it look like it wouldn't happen when is way too strong right now so I pretty much off limits
人员轮船最酷胃不舒服的十面埋伏是最具挑战性的是周六的它看起来像它不会发生在是太强烈，所以我现在几乎关闭的限制
11000 villages with gallery to witness system beeping on live television across China was growing and sake in the cold is Cam Newton Mississippi the top of the ceiling fan
11000个村，画廊见证系统发出蜂鸣声在中国各地的电视直播是在寒冷的成长和清酒是凸轮牛顿密西西比吊扇顶部
vapor pen describe the jump this could be anywhere in the weather so broke the clouds around the mouth
蒸汽笔形容跳跃，这可能是天气的任何地方，所以打破口周围的云层
clearance wind speeds a dropped uterus to real concerned about the turbulent air inside back crack in police seize the moment
间隙风速下子宫下降到真正的关心警察背隙里面的空气湍流抓紧时间
is chopper circle the mountain lining up for the precise angle to jump then he was flying down a hundred miles an hour and into the cracks between the raw
是菜刀圆山排队的精确的角度来跳，然后他飞下来一百英里的时速，并到原之间的裂痕
gospel round the valley to see a moon stone skate shoes for Hobbit safe landing on a mountaintop
福音圆谷看月亮石滑冰鞋霍比特人安全降落在山顶
coolest with extended single gnarliest my life without a doubt I have never ever experience more hardcore. AAA
最酷的带有扩展的单gnarliest我的生活毫无疑问，我从来没有经历过更多的铁杆。大中小
cheap cabs in Williams NBC News gentian China MSNBC nightly news for this Sunday coming up
威廉姆斯在NBC新闻便宜的出租车龙胆中国MSNBC晚间新闻这个星期天来了
pawn America Falcons Patriots game Brian Williams will be here tomorrow
典当美国猎鹰爱国者游戏布赖恩·威廉斯将在这里明天
I'm Lester Holt reporting from New York for all of us here is NBC News goodnight
我是莱斯特·霍尔特从纽约报道对我们所有在这里的是NBC新闻晚安